can I get to the Breaking Bad tonight racing down the underwater signals that seemed to indicate the missing jumbo jet
我可以给绝命毒今晚比赛下来水下的信号，似乎表明缺少大型喷气式客机
taking the stand and emotional Oscar Pistorius speaks directly to the parents of the woman he killed
采取的立场和情感奥斯卡·皮斯托留斯说直接把他杀死了女人的父母
family emergency a baby need of help the US Navy goes to the rescue and now the backlash against 2 para sailing around the world with two small children
家庭应急帮助宝宝需要美国海军去抢救，现在的反弹对世界各地的2款帆船带着两个孩子
can the epidemic destroying limes and families across our country denied a powerful personal looking for growing tall of heroin addiction also tonight on Hollywood legend has been lost nightly news now
可以疫情摧毁横跨我们的国家酸橙和家人否认了强大的个人寻找高成长海洛因成瘾今晚也对好莱坞传奇人物已经失去了现在夜间新闻
this is NBC Nightly News with Brian Williams
这是NBC晚间新闻与布赖恩·威廉斯
good evening its now been one month since flight 370 was last heard from Amwell the cable news coverage has called it breaking news for 30 days now
晚上好它现在过一次一个月以来飞行370最后一次听到Amwell有线新闻报道已经把它称为突发新闻30天了
the first real break a med midday Monday in Australia with word that the underwater sounds that vessels are picking up are consistent with the sounds
第一个真正的假期的MED周一午盘在澳洲与字，水下声音，船只拿起与声音一致
off the emergency beacon on a submerged widebody jetliner if this is indeed the wreckage it is several miles down and another long process will now begin but first
关闭在水下宽体客机的应急示位标，如果这是真实的残骸是几英里下来，又是漫长的过程现在开始，但第一
the race to confirm a fading sounds deep in the ocean we begin our coverage tonight NBC is Tom Costello
比赛进行到确认衰落的声音在海洋深处，我们开始我们今晚覆盖美国全国广播公司的汤姆·科斯特洛
ocean shield picture of something that sounds like this
的东西，这听起来像这样的海洋盾牌图片
underwater pinger attached
水下声波发射器连接
cost of pole for 2 hours 20 minutes before losing the signal will it take to settle up again at heard what sounded like two distinct 13th Street minutes search Commander say they could be from the black boxes
极2小时20分钟的成本失去信号前，会采取解决了再次听到声音听起来像是两个不同的13街分钟的搜寻指挥官说，他们可能是从黑盒子
liquid tights under eyes before the information is available to establish whether these the Texans can be concerned a stain from MI 370
根据眼睛的液体紧身衣的信息之前，请确定是否这些德州人可以从MI 370关注的污点
ICNA quarter nothing happens fast
ICNA季度没有任何反应快
long one of two or satellite connections to Madame possible flight paths
两个或卫星连接杜莎夫人可能飞行路径长个
Australian American teams location is 375 miles north of the Chinese navy reported hearing pains on Saturday given the distance expert say it's gone Lykke Li they're hearing the same signal for the Australian American team is cautiously optimistic
澳大利亚美国队的位置是北中国海军375英里报道听证会痛上周六给出的距离，专家说，它的消失Lykke李他们听到相同的信号为澳大利亚美国队是持谨慎乐观态度
would like to be able to tell the family said that we found a location but until we can reconfirm you know we we should not be to optimistic
希望能够告诉家人说，我们找到了一个位置，但直到我们可以再次确认您知道我们，我们不应该以乐观
more than a month since flight 370 vanished search team found crashed not a single piece of plane wreckage on the ocean surface complicated area of the Indian Ocean is 3 miles deep 14800 feet
一个多月以来航班370消失的搜索队发现失事不是一个单件平面残骸印度洋的海洋表面复杂的领域有3英里深14800英尺
equipment would be 14 Eiffel Tower statue on top of each other the very limit support the Navy's almond bluefin 21 submarine can operate to map the ocean floor
设备将是14艾菲尔铁塔雕像对方非常支持，限制了海军的杏仁黑21潜艇可以操作映射洋底顶部
get down there with you and photograph the entire debris field in Trion isolate those areas were the cockpit voice recorder in the flight data recorder might be located
趴下那里与你拍得了Trion整个碎片场隔离这些区域是驾驶舱语音记录器的飞行数据记录器可能位于
if they have her the actual pinger from the planes flight data in cockpit voice recorder experts say it could take several weeks to photograph a record
如果他们有她从驾驶舱语音记录专家的飞机飞行数据的实际平儿说，这可能需要几个星期的拍摄记录
the black boxes Dennis sumersible robot with claws retrieval in a best case scenario the entire process could take at least a month and maybe even longer Bryan
黑盒丹尼斯sumersible机器人用爪子检索在最好的情况下，整个过程可能需要至少一个月，甚至更长的布莱恩
Tom Costello & R Washington newsroom tonight on thanks it's important remember they were 239 passengers and crew onboard this flight and for their families this has been an awful waste again tonight NBC skating in Kuala Lumpur where the flight originated KD good evening
汤姆·科斯特洛＆R华盛顿编辑部今晚多亏这一点很重要记得他们是239名乘客和机组人员板载这次飞行和他们的家人这又是一个可怕的浪费，今晚美国全国广播公司溜冰在吉隆坡那里的飞行起源KD晚上好
Ryan family members of loved ones are trying not to get their hopes up saying that's with new news briefing it seems like there opening up opening up yet another wounded specially when they don't announce
亲人莱恩家族成员正试图不要让他们的希望说这是新的新闻发布会上好像有开放开辟的又一伤员特别是当他们不公布
the plane most of the Chinese family members who flew here to Malaysia demanding answers from official have gone back to Beijing worth today many holes a candlelight vigil mark in one month since the disappearance meanwhile transport official minister
飞机上的大部分中国家庭成员谁飞到这里来马来西亚官方要求的答案已经回到北京值得今天的许多漏洞在一个月烛光守夜活动标志，因为同时失踪的运输部长官
send once again that he is hoping for a miracle a hard thing from NYS here after the Prime Minister told them to
再次送他希望奇迹一个很难的事情从纽约州这里经过总理告诉他们
for the worst but brine without concrete evidence that the plane actually crash many are saying there's no reason to give up hope that their loved ones are still out there just waiting to be rescued
最坏的打算，但盐水没有具体的证据，这架飞机坠毁其实很多都是说没有理由放弃希望，他们的亲人仍然在那里等待被救出
gay teacher in Kuala Lumpur tonight running out our coverage of this town jetliner Katy thanks
在吉隆坡同性恋老师今晚不多了我们的覆盖这个小镇客机的凯蒂感谢
in this country this evening we are watching another system of severe weather after a rolled through the SE in Covington County Mississippi their assessing the damage from the tornado that hit Burley this morning Weather Channel meteorologist Mike Seidel is there for us tonight
在这个国家今天晚上我们正在看的恶劣天气的另一个系统后，通过SE在科文顿县密西西比推出自己的评估从龙卷风袭击白肋烟今天上午天气频道的气象学家迈克·赛德尔是给我们今晚的损害
fibroid get into you how does the Deep South beginning early this morning before sunrise I'm here in Covington County Mississippi the results for devastating
子宫肌瘤进入你如何在南方开始今天凌晨日出前我在这里在Covington县密西西比的结果毁灭性的
Nef to tornado with winters high is 125 miles per hour touchdown on the road community of hot coffee Mississippi in Covington County residents could even react
奈夫龙卷风与冬季高为125英里每小时的触地得分在热咖啡密西西比州科文顿县居民路社区甚至可能反应
Illinois a boom trailer repair my toilet fill out public
伊利诺伊州的繁荣拖车修理我的厕所填写公
the early morning storm destroy nearly three homes into the roof off doesnt Moore leaving down power lines in its wake 7 people were injured
清晨风暴摧毁了近三口之家在车顶关闭不穆尔离开停运电力线路在其身后7人受伤
Jackson Mississippi 7 inches of rain turns into lakes in force people to abandon their cars
杰克逊密西西比7英寸雨水变成湖泊迫使人们放弃他们的汽车
I had to come and knock on peoples doors just to get them to come back to add to cart before the to Commander
我只好来敲门，门人民只是为了让他们回来添加到购物车之前，指挥官
the heavy rain in Yazoo City Mississippi created a flash flood sweeping a 9 year old girl away from her parents night desserts continues in Birmingham Alabama the surgeon water stone out sim card in an apartment complex have to be a vacuolated
在亚祖市密西西比大雨创造了山洪席卷一9岁女孩远离她的父母晚上甜品在阿拉巴马州伯明翰继续操刀水石出SIM卡中的公寓大楼必须是一个空泡
pictures to send this evening of a reported twister in Eastern North Carolina
图片发在东部北卡罗来纳州报告的龙卷风今晚
na tornado watch continuum
呐龙卷风手表连续
Florida Georgia and the Carolinas
佛罗里达州佐治亚和卡罗来纳
Mike Seidel reporting in the South like a bad weather like from Mississippi Mike Sykes today in South Africa former Olympic track star Oscar Pistorius took the stand for the first time facing charges he intentionally shot and killed his girlfriend reeva Steenkamp last year
迈克·赛德尔在南方报像一个糟糕的天气怎么样从密西西比迈克·赛克斯今天在南非前奥运田径明星奥斯卡·皮斯托留斯采取了立场，首次面临指控他故意开枪打死了他的女朋友reeva Steenkamp去年
an emotionally addressing members of her family
她的家人的情感回应委员
we get more from NBC's Mike Taibbi who was there in the courtroom in Pretoria
我们从NBC的迈克·泰比谁在那里在比勒陀利亚法庭上得到更多的
when Oscar Pistorius walk to the witness box juicing not to give a testimony on camera use a price of Court fight turn into the family of reeva Steenkamp to apologize
当奥斯卡皮斯托留斯走到证人席榨汁不给相机见证使用的宫廷斗争之交的价格进入reeva Steenkamp的家人道歉
Wikipedia
维基百科
Huntsman cheese
亨斯迈奶酪
compose the bridge wind speed does not your fault love
构成桥风速不你的错爱
with his family looking on the story a struggle with his emotions killing Steenkamp my farming 4 shot through a locked bathroom door thinking she was an intruder a tragic mistake
与他的家人在寻找的故事，他的情绪斗争进行上锁的卫生间门杀Steenkamp我养殖4射门以为她是入侵者一个悲剧性的错误
I have to f***
我到f *​​*
things that happen in Knoxville
事情发生在诺克斯维尔
wake up to being 25
醒来的时候，即25
the former Olympic track star Merced to have a short temper and love of guns did they told the court he now lives in constant fear
前奥运田径明星默塞德有一个脾气暴躁和爱枪没有他们在法庭上说，他现在生活在恐惧中
son of God
神的儿子
Pistorius will be back on the stand tomorrow the only person who knows what happened that night trying to convince the court is telling the truth
皮斯托留斯将回到待机明天谁知道发生了什么事，当晚试图说服法庭的唯一的人是说真话
Mike Taibbi NBC News Pretoria South Africa
迈克·泰比NBC新闻比勒陀利亚南​​非
in light of today's testimony we are happy to welcome the newest member of R&B singers family are senior legal correspondent Cynthia McFadden welcome to you and I because this was a big day in this case interview
鉴于今天的证词，我们很高兴地欢迎的R＆B歌手家族的最新成员都是资深的法律记者辛西娅·麦克法登欢迎你和我，因为这是一个大日子在这种情况下采访
did he help himself what's so far today of horses friendly questioning rhyme with his lawyer he was trying to present himself as a man of good character comb person
他才帮自己今天什么马到目前为止友好韵质疑与他的律师，他正试图把自己打扮成品格良好，梳子的人一个人
how to get me to the judge what matters most is what is yet to come will you be able to keep it cooler will you show himself to be the kind of person
如何让我的判断最重要的是什么都还没来，你才能够保持它凉会告诉你自己是什么样的人
who could have in a fit of anger
谁可能在气头上
savage Lee murdered his girlfriend
李野蛮谋杀了他的女友
great to have you here we will be watching it all welcome to night
伟大的，有你在这里，我们将密切关注这一切欢迎到夜间
Ematic rescue playing out in the Pacific Ocean a family of 4 sailing around the world got into trouble when they're sailboat broke down and they are 1 year old eat youngest of two children on board got seriously ill
Ematic救援玩出太平洋一家在世界各地航行4陷入困境时，他们的帆船坏了，他们是1岁吃最小的两个孩子在船上生了重病
it's all lead to a massive military effort to reach them tonight the families on their way home omits some harsh judgement against the parents
这一切都导致了大规模的军事行动，以达成今晚他们在归途中省略了对父母的一些严苛的评判家属
are report on all of its an eye from NBC is Miguel Almaguer
对所有其从NBC眼睛的报告米格尔Almaguer
the rescue was dramatic
救援是巨大的
first California Air National Guard plunging into the middle of the Pacific
第一加州空军国民警卫队陷入太平洋中部
the crew Barneys crippled sailboat than whiskey to wear young family bringing them aboard a Navy war vessel turned rescue ship and I think some people like
船员巴尼斯残废帆船比威士忌穿的年轻家庭把他们的一艘海军舰艇转身救援船，我觉得有些人喜欢
some people vote for Eric and Charlotte Kaufman the trip again as a journey around the globe with their small children 3 year old Cora in one year old lyrics
有些人再次投票埃里克和夏洛特·考夫曼的行程为世界各地的旅程与他们的孩子小3岁的科拉在一岁歌词
thanks for watching and I buy
感谢收看，我买
what nine hundred miles off the coast of Mexico travel 36 foot sailboat lost power and steering lira with seriously ill amazing lyrics doing great um she is responding well
什么900英里离墨西哥海岸游36英尺的帆船失去动力和转向里拉与重病惊人的歌词做伟大嗯，她反应良好
tonight baby lyrics is in good condition and we now know the Kaufmans won't have to pay for the rescue what they face a wave of criticism and outrage on social media
今晚宝贝歌词是在良好的条件，我们现在知道了考夫曼不会有什么，他们面临一波的批评和愤怒在社交媒体来支付救援
we're all entitled to your own opinion I'm sorry that there's criticism I fink sailing with children is a justmine ideas
我们都有权享有自己的观点我很遗憾，还有批评我芬克帆船儿童是一个justmine思路
tymir Lee over but there is still plenty of drama about this boy
tymir李结束了，但仍然有大量的戏剧这个男孩
in the open sea Miguel Almaguer NBC News San Diego
在公海上米格尔Almaguer NBC新闻圣迭戈
steelhead on a Monday night broadcast the epidemic sweeping across parts of this country a desperate situation in so many American cities and towns caught in the grip of pills can I take racing and personal wake up call
虹鳟在周一晚上播出的流行在这个国家的部分地区席卷在众多的美国城市和城镇陷入了药丸的抓地力绝望的境地，我可以把赛车和个人敲响了警钟
he was the biggest movie star on the planet first time remembering the legendary wanna be all by my little bro
他是最大的电影明星在这个星球第一次想起了传说中想通过我的小兄弟将所有
tonight here we began a series of reports across all platforms of NBC News examining the origins and growing heroin problem in our country the numbers are staggering Elbert just a five-year period heroin abuse has nearly doubled in America
今晚我们在这里开始了一系列的跨越NBC新闻的所有平台报告审查的起源和我国日益增长的海洛因问题的数字是惊人的埃尔伯特短短五年期海洛因滥用情况几乎在美国一倍
tonight we're going to begin our reporting in New England because it's a snapshot of what's on folding and communities across the country if so bad in parts of Vermont
今晚我们将开始我们的新英格兰地区的报告，因为它是一个什么样的对全国各地的折叠和社区的快照，如果这么严重的佛蒙特州部分地区
shear that states governor devoted his entire state of the state to this one topic the epidemic calling it a full blown heroin prices
剪切，指出州长投入的状态他的整个状态，这一个主题疫情称这是一个完全成熟的海洛因价格
we get our report tonight from national correspondent
我们从国家的记者让我们今晚的报告
look past the lighthouses in covered bridges as we drove through we found another New England wear a bucket of used heroin needles at a needle exchange one afternoon measures the scale of the problem in Portland Maine when did you start feeling up
看看过去在廊桥的灯塔，因为我们开车经过，我们发现你是什么时候开始感觉另一个新英格兰佩戴使用海洛因针的桶一个针具交换一个下午措施的问题的规模在缅因州波特兰
this bucket with change this morning so just from today
这桶变今早所以只是从今天开始
parent support each other in Salem Massachusetts
家长支持对方在马萨诸塞州塞勒姆
2000 Alero minutes away in the Walmart parking lot in quiet room
2000阿莱罗分钟的路程在沃尔玛的停车场安静的房间
Vermont is known as the place with 20 bucks buy a ticket local slang for small baggie of heroin the number of people dying from a heroin overdose
佛蒙特州被称为20块钱的地方买票当地俚语的小旅行箱海洛因的人吸食海洛因过量死亡人数
Vermont more than doubled in just one year all over the state there a waiting list to get into treatment clinics like Green Mountain family medicine
佛蒙特州超过全州各地有等候名单进入治疗诊所像绿山家庭医学在短短一年内翻了一番
the the downhill spiral I was so fast
在下坡的螺旋我是如此之快
how much do I have in my life Dr Dean McKenzie says heroine has a grip on this town
多少钱我有我的生活院长麦肯齐博士说女主角对这个小镇一握
after while you're not doing it get high you do not survive
而你不这样做后，获得高你就无法生存
you do not see don't get sick
你没有看到不生病
give his wife dr. Cheryl McKenzie is in the same field a psychologist a live in a beautiful home in the mountains with their young kids to Katonah to Rutland
给老婆博士。谢丽尔麦肯齐是在同一领域的心理学家一个住在一个美丽的家在山与他们的年轻孩子凯托纳拉特兰
couple dealers on this road right here on this road with the kid on the road again because I've bought there before
在这条路上就在这个道路的道路上孩子的夫妇经销商再次，因为我之前有买
that's right in the Son of parents to dedicate their lives to fighting substance abuse the secret me hooked on heroin while living in their home the boy who did a bookworm
这是正确的父母的儿子献出自己的生命去战斗物质滥用我迷上秘密海洛因住在他们家谁做了书呆子的男生，而
great student join the Model UN High School started using prescription painkillers and got addicted to those what pills have become harder to come by in Vermont
伟大的学生参加模拟联合国高中开始使用处方止痛药，得到了沉迷于那些什么丸已成为难以在佛蒙特州得的
my dealer can get them anymore so I couldn't get them and then as I couldn't get an error when starting to move in
我的经销商可以得到它们了，所以我不能让他们再为开始移动，当我不能得到一个错误
she's a jet engine
她是一个喷气发动机
Aron and down from there
阿隆，并从那里下来
when Ryan confessed he was addicted Cheryl went through his room
当赖安供述他沉迷谢丽尔通过自己的房间去
soundowl needles and spoons spoons we're going and I get really thought that maybe we the kids for throwing them out with their plates no that's not really stands for going your doctors
soundowl针和勺子勺子，我们要去和我得到真正想，也许我们的孩子扔出来用自己的盘子不，这不是真的代表你去医生
work parents
家长工作
is very easy to try to put on your dock
很容易就尽量把你的码头
parents were just like any other parent who's dealing with someone with an addiction
父母就像任何其他的父母谁在处理人与瘾
Brian tells if he's been clean for a year as a blessed weekend love your son clearly I dont like
布莱恩告诉他一直干净了一年的周末祝福爱你的儿子显然我不喜欢
translate only time she loves the state to work in with other to cross the Rutland community to change what's happening here
只翻译时，她所热爱的国家一道，与其他穿越拉特兰社会来改变这里发生了什么
everytime we go to a meeting it gets bigger and bigger and that's what we need to see happen people who are the Texans to c** hard ask for help
每次我们去开会也变得越来越大，而这正是我们需要看到发生的人谁是德州人到c **难求人
don't be embarrassed
不要不好意思，
we heard so many times I swore and right now is because people who started abusing prescription painkillers found heroin
我们听到很多次，我发誓而现在是因为人们谁开始滥用处方止痛药发现海洛因
are the cheaper alternatives for families dealing with addiction
是家庭应对瘾便宜的替代品
resources on our website nbcnews.com and you can share how heroin has touched your life using hashtags heroin in America
在我们的网站nbcnews.com，你可以分享如何海洛因使用主题标签海洛因在美国碰到你的生活资源
Osaka sauna miracle remedy for an overdose but it is not legal everywhere yet so we need a mother is so desperate for this
大阪桑拿奇迹补救过量，但它是不合法的还随处可见，所以我们需要一个母亲是如此渴望这个
going to break the law Brian and Chip potentially safe and that's the thing about this powerful reporting this weekend
要犯法Brian和芯片潜在的安全，这就是关于这个强大的报表的东西本周末
women along the way to all remind us of someone Kate snow thanks will see right back here tomorrow night and we're back in the moment with the news today about the end of an era
沿途所有的妇女提醒我们有人凯特雪感谢会看到右后卫位置在明天晚上，我们又回来在当下的消息，今天约一个时代的终结
the people who track the status on airline performance say despite worsening on time performance and lost bags complaints are down these days because of an increase in apathy among us passengers who come to assume the performances just going to get worse every year
谁跟踪航空公司业绩状况的人说，尽管恶化的时间性能和丢失的行李的投诉是因为我们的乘客谁前来承担演出只是会变得更糟，每年中增加淡漠下来，这些天
we put the entire list of airlines on our website for the second year in a row Virgin America was rated best wall American Eagle fell 4 spots on the list and place last
我们把航空公司的整个列表在我们网站上的一排维珍美国的第二年被评为最好的墙体美国之鹰跌4点清单，并在去年上
somebody one Smart Car tipping in San Francisco believed to be just a prank and not a broader statement about smart cars if anything of course the bay area is known for being so environmentally conscious but that doesn't stop a group of young man
在旧金山人1智​​能汽车倾翻认为只是一个恶作剧，并没有关于智能汽车更广阔的语句，如果当然任何事物的海湾地区是著名的如此环保意识，但并不能阻止一群年轻人
Spotify 1 witness how long around one of the Smart cars and has a setting it on its hind legs police are investigating
Spotify的1见证如何围绕智能汽车的一长有它的后腿警方设置它正在调查
no no one in the industry actually believes that will really happen Barbara Walters retiring as now set a date for last appearance on The View will be May 16 she is 84 she will continue as a
没有任何人在行业中真正相信会有这样的情况芭芭拉沃尔特斯退休作为现在设置为最后一次出现在该视图的日期将是5月16日，她是84，她将继续作为一个
retirement may remain a relative
退休可能会保持一个相对的
the 8 month old
8个月大
tricking of England that the British papers have taken the calling Gorgeous George what does parents in New Zealand all 3 look now the worse for wear as George made his public debut on foreign soil with his mother wearing a color red the park and back to Diana's visit
英格兰的欺骗，英国报纸已经采取主叫华丽的乔治什么呢父母在新西兰所有3看看现在穿的更差，因为乔治做了他的首次公开亮相在异国他乡与他的母亲穿着颜色红公园和回戴安娜的访问
sex change the traditional rubbing noses greeting they were greeted by one of those extraordinary Maori warriors with tattooed legs and not much else and it was great to see Prince
性别改变了传统的揉鼻子问候他们由其中的一个非凡的毛利武士纹身与腿和没有多少人迎接，这是很高兴地看到王子
carrying the coveted kangaroo backpack when we come back remembering a legend on a career
承载着令人垂涎的袋鼠背包的时候，才想起回来了职业生涯的一个传说
finally here tonight he was durable he out lives in outlast of most of his peers and he was indelible there was nobody else quite like Mickey Rooney and when we learned late last night that he had died at the end of a 9 decades career
终于来了，今晚他是耐用的，他出生活中的大多数他的同龄人拖垮，他不可磨灭没有其他人很喜欢米奇鲁尼，当我们得知昨晚深夜，他在9数十年的职业生涯结束已经死亡
NetSpend just about the entire record in history of motion pictures all the way to present day
到现今NetSpend只是在电影史上的整个记录​​一路
PL blasted pretty much everyone from what people affectionately call old Hollywood and right up to the end million still picture Mickey Rooney from his early pictures as a young and Susie ask a guy with a twinkle in his eye
PL从人们亲切地称呼老好莱坞一直到年底万元静止图像米奇鲁尼从他早期的照片与他的眼睛一眨一对年轻和苏西问一个家伙轰出几乎每个人都
back in the day he was known as the most famous teenager in America back when it meant a lot to spend a quarter to go to the movies he meant a lot to Depression era audience
早在他被称为最有名的小将在美国回来时，它意味着很多花四分之一去他的意思了很多萧条时代的观众看电影的日子
I'm just a very lucky what is a jewel who had the opportunity that God gave me
我只是一个很幸运的是宝石谁的机会，上帝给了我
to be in a business that I adore and love and get paid on welfare
要在一个企业，我崇拜和爱和福利得到报酬
child star was an understatement who was on the phone bill stay Jessup toddler shot his
童星是一个轻描淡写谁在电话账单停留杰塞普幼儿枪杀了他
first movie in 86 when full grown eBay really cracked 53 which was always whine when he was playing young guys with full faces
在86的第一部电影时，生长完全的eBay真的破获53时，他被打的年轻球员充分的面孔总是抱怨
later in life 6 inches taller Mickey Rooney's life was also rambling wreck interrupted by moments of great success
后来在寿命6英寸高米奇鲁尼的生活也是东拉西扯沉船由巨大的成功时刻中断
he made in lost of Fortune several times over Kenny famously spend a lot of his life looking for love he married 8 times Ava Gardner
他在失去的财富提出了若干倍肯尼著名花了很多他的生活中寻找爱他娶了8倍艾娃·加德纳
Mangham on screen has material range from Shakespeare to the modern-day Muppets and he famously played alongside Spencer Tracy and Elizabeth
Mangham在屏幕上有材料范围从莎士比亚到现代的提线木偶和他著名的一起玩斯潘塞特雷西和伊丽莎白
Taylor and Judy Garland his co star in 30 showtimes I wonder if it's all worth while
泰勒和朱迪·加兰他在30场次合作明星我不知道如果这一切都值得
in so many interviews for his heart on his sleeve and spoke the truth about Hollywood and AJ
在这么多的面试他的心脏在他的袖子，说真话好莱坞和AJ
and late in life you enjoyed wearing his world war 2 medals on his chest including a Bronze Star for entertaining the troops in combat zones
后期在生活中你喜欢穿着他的世界战争2枚奖牌在他的胸口，包括铜星娱乐的部队在战斗中区
he was nominated for an Oscar for time
他被提名为奥斯卡时间
what the role of the brown M&M in a Golden Globe late in life when he played a man named Bill who spent 46 years in a mental hospital
什么的棕色M＆M在金球奖在晚年时，他扮演一个叫比尔的人谁了46年的精神病院中的作用
apartment 1 Everett gets tired of life
公寓1埃弗雷特厌倦生活
I wish I were in love again Mickey Rooney was remembered today as impression irrepressible a man who always found work because it all went back to putting on a show
我希望我是在爱再次米奇鲁尼今天记住作为抑制不住的印象总是谁找到工作，一个人，因为这一切又回到作秀
the indelible and durable Mickey Rooney was 93 years old
不可磨灭的耐用米奇鲁尼为93岁
that is our broadcast on a Monday night as we start of this new week thank you for being here with us as always on Brian Williams we hope to see right back here tomorrow evening good night
这是我们的广播在周一晚上当我们开始这个新的一周感谢您能在这里和我们一如既往的布赖恩·威廉斯，我们希望看到的右后卫位置明晚晚安